Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series B. Arbitration Files
    - Barrett, Haentjens and Company vs. International Molders and Allied Workers Union of North America, Local 422, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      7/31/1967; #14-30-0764-66 Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Barrett, Haentjens and Company vs. International Molders and Allied Workers Union of North America, Local 422, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      4/17/1968; #14-30-0153-68 Settled.
    - Baseball Clubs, Major Leagues of Professional vs. Major League Baseball Players Association, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      2/19/1974; Various Materials.
    - Baseball Clubs, Major Leagues of Professional vs. Major League Baseball Players Association, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      12/16/1974; Withdrawn.
    - Bassick Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 229, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      2/2/1954; #L-10611 NY-L-188-53 Issues: Suspension; Improper Job Attitude.
    - Bassick Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 229, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      3/15/1963; #L-35635 HART-L-136-62 Issues: Shift Scheduling; Transfers.
    - Bassick Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 229, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      6/14/63; L-37437 HART-L-42-63 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - Bassick Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 229, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      8/14/1964; #L-41227-HART-L-23-64 Issues: Transfers; Seniority.
    - Bassick Division, Stewart-Warner Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 229, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      1/13/1971; #71A/1560 Issues: Layoffs; Bumping.
    - Beaunit Fibers, Division of Beaunit Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 20, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      3/22/1967; #15-30-0132-66 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Becton, Dickinson and Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 481, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      8/27/57; #56-254 Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Bee Line Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 252, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      5/27/1955; Issues: Overtime; Premium Pay.
    - Bee Line Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 252, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      10/23/1956; No Decision - Order Staying Arbitration.
    - Bell Container vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, District 65, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      10/8/54; #L-13209 NY-L-449-54 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      5/19/1971; #14-30-0935-70M Issues: Discharge; Plant Rules.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      11/4/1971; #14-30-066-71M-J Issues: Backpay Award; Discharge.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      2/19/1973; #14-30-0177-72 M-P Issues: Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages; Damages.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      3/4/1973; #14-30-1000-72 M-P No Decision - Hearing Notes.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      4/11/1974; #14-30-0068-74 M-C Issues: Discharge; Plant Rules.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      6/21/1974; #14-30-0565-73 M-C Issues: Demotion; Disability.
    - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      1/17/1975; #14-30-1000-72 M-C No Decision.
    - Belmont Smelting., 1969 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      5/19/69; Postponed
    - Bendix Aviation Corporation, Eclipse - Pioneer Division vs. Aircraft Workers Union of New Jersey, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      6/6/1957; #56-173 Issue: Elimination of Jobs.
    - Berger Machine and Tool Company, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      3/15/1956; #55-136 Settled.
    - Bethlehem Fabricators, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      4/10/1974; #14-30-0978-73C Withdrawn.
    - Bethlehem Mines Corporation vs. United Mine Workers of America, District 2, Local 1368, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      10/31/1973; #33-13 Issues: Call-in Pay; Equipment and Physical Facilities.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      5/21/1961; Arbitration Materials.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      1/23/1964; #B-5946 Issue: Job Evaluation.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      1/23/1964; #B-6872 Issues: Suspension; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      1/31/1964; #B-4940 and B-6601 Issues: Layoffs; Seniority.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      2/17/1964; #B-5743 Issues: Past Practice; Assignment of Jobs.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      4/28/1964; #B-7558 Issue: Safety.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      4/28/1964; #7642 Issues: Suspension; Rules; Safety.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      4/30/1964; #H-352 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      5/9/1964; #B-7373 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      5/9/1964; #B-7601 No Decision.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      5/25/1964; #D-9134 Issue: Elimination of Jobs.
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2604, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      5/27/1964; #A-7345 and D-9136 Issue: Crew Size.
    - Bilt Rite Baby Carriage Company vs. Furniture Workers Union, Local 76-B, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      11/18/1949; L-5499 NY-L-283-49 Issues: Management's Rights; Discipline.
    - Black Clawson Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 137, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      5/13/1966; #66A/2607 Settled.
    - Bloomingdales Department Store vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, District 65, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      2/18/1957; #L-17890 NY-L-470-56 Issues: Discharge; Falsification.
    - Bloomingdales Department Store vs. United Storeworkers, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      8/21/1971; #1330-0540-71 Withdrawn.
    - Bond Baking Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 835, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      5/4/1976; Settled.
    - Boyle - Midway Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 3-531, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      7/7/1971; #71A/5927 Issue: Equipment and Physical Facilities.
    - Bristol Brass Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1500, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      9/18/1969; #12-30- 0043-69 Issues: Transfers; Seniority; Overtime.
    - Bristol Brass Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1500, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      9/18/1969; #12-30- 0062-69 Issues: Super seniority; Transfers.
    - Brooklyn Hospital vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      6/10/1970; #1330-0291-70 Issues: Discharge; Suspension; Insubordination.
    - Budd Company vs. Independent Workers Union of the Budd Company, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      11/10/1959; L-24210 PHI-L-132-59 Issues: Layoffs; Seniority.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      7/25/1962; #PHI-L-64-62 Issues: Layoffs; Seniority. Settled.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      9/15/1962; #L-33581-PHI-L-73- 62 Issue: Bumping.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 92, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      9/19/1962; #L-33934-PHI-L-143- 62 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Budd Company vs. Technical, Office and Professional Workers Union, Local 757, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      12/12/1962; #L-33997-PHI-L-164-62 Settled.
    - Budd Company vs. Technical, Office and Professional Workers Union, Local 757, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      4/18/1963; #L-34002-PHI-L-169-62 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Budd Company vs. Technical, Office and Professional Workers Union, Local 757, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      10/25/1963; #L-37744-PHI-L-184-63 Settled.
    - Budd Company vs. Technical, Office and Professional Workers Union, Local 757, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      2/14/1966; #L-42962-PHI-L-376-64 Issues: Compensation; Bonuses; Absence.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 14)
      3/19/1966; #L-47012-PHI-L- 411-65 Issues: Employee Rights; Shift Scheduling.
    - Budd Company vs. Technical, Office and Professional Workers Union, Local 757, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      5/19/1969; #14-30-0692-68 Issues: Suspension; Improper Personal Conduct; Improper Work Practices; Plant Rules.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 16)
      3/28/1969; #14-30-0815-68 Withdrawn.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      6/7/1969; #14-30-0097-69M Issue: Recall.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      6/19/1969; #14-30-0177-69 Issues: Suspension; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      1/17/1970; #14-30-0727-67 Issues: Recall; Notification.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813 -, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      2/28/70; #14-30-0084-70 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      6/15/1970; #14-30-0042-71 M- J Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      11/16/1971; #14-30-0608-71 M-J Withdrawn.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1287, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      1/4/1972; #1430-1032-71 M-J Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 24)
      8/9/1972; #1430-0869-72 M-J Issue: Notification.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 25)
      12/18/1972; #1430-0121-73 M-J Settled. Issues: Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Budd Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 813, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 26)
      3/28/1973; Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Buena Vista Construction Company vs. International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Workers and United Scenic Artists, Local 829, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 27)
      10/28/1971; #L-47095 SYR-L-93-65 Issues: Holidays; Part Time Employees.
    - Buffalo Courier Express, Inc. vs. Newspaper Guild of Buffalo, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      1/4/1966; #70A-8138 Settled.
    - Bullard Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7528, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 29)
      10/13/70; #14-30-0203-69 Issues: Vacation Pay; Termination of Employment.
    - Bureau of National Affairs vs. Washington - Baltimore Guild, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 30)
      10/30/1969; Settled.
    - Buxton, Inc. vs. International Leather Goods, Plastic and Novelty Workers Union, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 31)
      2/23/1973; #14-30-0377-67 Issues: Bargaining Unit; Classification of Jobs.
    - Caloric Corporation vs. International Molders and Allied Workers Union of North America, Local 114, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      10/19/1967; #14-30-0377-67 Issues: Bargaining Unit; Classification of Jobs.
    - Capital District Transportation Authority vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1321, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      10/25/1975; Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 527, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      1/11/1968; #67A/3752 Withdrawn.
    - Carrier Corporation vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 527, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      6/15/1971; Issue: Promotions.
    - Catalin Corporation of America vs. Federal Labor Union, Local 22026, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      7/1/1957; #56-275 Issues: Overtime; Classification of Jobs.
    - Caterpillar Tractor Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 786, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      12/28/1962; Issues: Assignment of Jobs; Classification of Jobs.
    - Celotex Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 127, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      7/26/1968; #1430-0798-67 Issue: Classification of Jobs.
    - Chalfin Machine Products, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1614, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      6/9/1954; #AR8594 Issue: Arbitrability.
    - Chapin and Bangs Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      8/8/1972; #12 30 0060 72 Issues: Discharge; Incompetence and Inefficiency; Improper Job Attitude.
    - Children' Theater, Producers' Association of vs. Actors and Artists of America, Associated, Actors' Equity Association (AAA-AEA), 1971 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      8/3/1971; #1330-0706-71 Issue: Definitions.
    - Club Transportation Corporation vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America (AASER & MCEA), Local 1134, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      1/11/1950; Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness; Threat.
    - Club Transportation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 100, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      3/25/1949; Settled.
    - Coca Cola Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 125, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      6/5/1967; Issue: Posting.
    - Coggins Chevrolet, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Local 335, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      10/9/1972; Issue: Duty to Bargain.
    - Colt's, Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 376, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      1/18/1970; #12-30-0106-70 Issues: Suspension; Discharge; Inefficiency.
    - Colt's Inc. vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 376, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      11/10/1972; #12-30-0119-72 Withdrawn.
    - Connecticut Railway and Lighting Company vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees Association, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      3/20/1961; Fact-finding.
    - Consolidated Edison Company of N.Y., Inc. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      10/3/1960; Issues: Discharge; Fights and Altercations.
    - Container Corporation of America vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Local 520, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      10/11/1967; #15-30-0016-67 Issues: Suspension; Absences.
    - Container Corporation of America vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 807, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      5/8/1972; #14-30-0021-71 R Withdrawn.
    - Continental Can Company - Agreements, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      Dec. 62
    - Continental Can Company - Steelworkers: General, 1962-1968 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      12/6/1962; #19-303 Issues: Employee Rights; Promotions.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant 6 and 32 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      1/10/1963; #33-62-38 Settled.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      1/17/1963; #19-298 Issues: Employee Rights; Promotions.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      1/18/1963; #19-282 Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Supervisors and Foremen.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      3/18/1963; #19-362 No Decision. Issue: Overtime.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant 6, Metal Division R & D (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      7/3/1963; #6-62-2 No Decision.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 (Maspeth, New York) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      7/12/1963; #19- 309
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      8/18/1963; #19-277 and #19-293A Issue: Recall.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 (Maspeth, New York) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      9/11/1963; #19-283 Issues: Recall; Seniority; Transfer.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #16 (Baltimore, Maryland) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4340, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      9/5/1963; #500 No Decision. Issue: Overtime.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #16 (Baltimore, Maryland) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4340, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      10/23/1963; #502 Issue: Reporting Pay.
    - Continental Can Company, Metropolitan Plant #19 (Maspeth, New York) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5640, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      10/28/1963; #19- 345 Issue: Insurance Plans.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #86 (Reading, Pennsylvania) vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      1/20/1964; #86-137 Withdrawn.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #48 (Paterson, New Jersey) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3913, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      2/1/1964; #48-397 No Decision.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #5 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2374, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      4/6/1964; #5-62-42 Issue: Rate Retention.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #5 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2374, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      4/7/1964; #5-63-52 No Decision.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #5 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2374, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      4/6/1964; #5-63-52 Withdrawn.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #6 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      7/6/1964; #6-64-3 Decision Lacking.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #17 & 58 (Tampa) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4939, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      7/15/64.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4117, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      11/9/1964; Opinion Missing.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      11/9/1964; #33-63-29 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      11/10/1964; #33-64-14 Opinion Missing.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      11/11/1964; #33-63-38 No Opinion.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      9/17/1964; #33-64-24 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #37A (Pascagoula, Mississippi) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5834, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1965; #63-4A Issue: Contracting Out.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #77 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4454, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      4/19/1965; #77-63-38 Issue: Benefit Plans.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #77 (Milwaukee, Wisconsin) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4454, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      4/19/1965; #77-63-9 Issue: Insurance.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #6 (McDonald, Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3042, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      8/6/1965; #6-64-3 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #5 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2374, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      8/9/1965; #5-64-12 Issue: Pension Plans.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #64 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2645, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      8/9/1965; #64-64-22 & #64-64-23 Issue: Garnishments.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #73 (St. Louis) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1120, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      11/17/1965; #73-65-22 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #33 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4117, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      12/30/1965; #33-65-C51 Issues: Discharge; Absenteeism; Tardiness.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #950 (Shoreham, Michigan) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6264, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      2/16/1966; #950-65-21 Issues: Shift Scheduling; Seniority.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #80 (Pittsburg, California) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5084, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      3/11/1966; #30-C80-65 No Opinion.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #11 (Los Angeles, California) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1502, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      3/14/1966; #36-C11-65 Issues: Suspension; Inability to Work; Overtime.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #64 (Chicago) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2645, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      12/22/1966; #64-65-12 Issue: Overtime.
    - Continental Can Company, Plant #73 (St. Louis, Missouri) vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1120, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      12/14/1966; #73-65-5 & 73-65-6 Issues: Compensation; Shift Scheduling.